Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Events
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- General Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Activities, 1939-present
  - "Annette Lemieux- Artists Gallery Talks", November 17, 1988; PERSONALITY: Annette Lemieux SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Pam Heller, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Annette Lemieux, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Clyfford Still RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.96)
  - "James Wines - Artists Gallery Talks", November 17, 1988; PERSONALITY: James Wines SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Marco Pasanella, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; James Wines, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Sound quality very bad; sound drops out frequently throughout beginning of talk (Item 98.97)
  - "Richard Bosman -Artists Gallery Talks", November 17, 1988; PERSONALITY: Richard Bosman SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Anna Marie Shapiro, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Richard Bosman, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Redon, Bonnard, Ensor, Rousseau RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.98)
  - "Peter Campus - Artists Gallery Talks", November 17, 1988; PERSONALITY: Peter Campus SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context: Artist Talks in the Galleries PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Susan Saltz, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Peter Campus, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Arshile Gorky RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.99, 98.99D)
  - "Pentimenti: The Art of Richard Diebenkorn", December 1, 1988; PERSONALITY: John 2 PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: John Elderfield, Director, Department of Drawings, The Museum of Modern Art SPONSOR: The Bohen Foundation; New York State Council of the Arts EXHIBITION:The Drawings of Richard Diebenkorn(November 17, 1988- January 10, 1989) MoMA Exh. #1503 DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Lecture given in conjunction with exhibition DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.100)
  - "Gallery Talk", January 4, 1989; DATA: One 60-minute Standard Audio Cassette (both sides) SUMMARY: Gallery talk [?] Side I: Picasso:Guitar, 1912;Glass of Absinthe, 1914;Three Musicians, 1921;Three Women at the Spring, 1921; Leger:Three Women, 1921; Brancusi Sculpture Side II: Brancusi Sculpture; Chagall:I and the Village, 1911; Kirchner:Street, Dresden; Street Berlin RELATED MATERIAL: 98.102 DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.101)
  - "Gallery talk", January 4, 1989; DATA: One 60-minute Standard Audio Cassette (side I only) SUMMARY: Gallery talk [?] Side I: Kirchner:Street, Berlin; Kokoschka:M/M Tietze; Nolde:Lehmbruck; Mondrian Gallery RELATED MATERIAL: 98.101 DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.102)
  - "Steven Holl Lecture- Anchoring", March 7, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Stuart Wrede, Director, Department of Architecture and Design, The Museum of Modern Art; Steven Holl, architect, Associate Professor, Columbia Graduate School of Architecture SPONSOR: Gerald D. Hines Interests Architecture Program EXHIBITION:Emilio Ambasz/Steven Holl[MoMA Exh. #1511, February 9-April 4, 1989] DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette (both sides) SUMMARY: First of two lectures given in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.104a, 98.104b DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Sound quality is poor; there is a buzzing sound throughout lecture (Item 98.103)
  - "Emilio Ambasz Lecture: Poetics of the Pragmatic", March 14, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, 1989 PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Stuart Wrede, Director, Department of Architecture and Design, The Museum of Modern Art; Emilio Ambasz, architect SPONSOR: Gerald D. Hines Interests Architecture Program EXHIBITION:Emilio Ambasz/Steven Holl[MoMA Exh. #1511, February 9-April 4, 1989] DATA: Two 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (tape I: both sides; tape II: side I only) SUMMARY: Second of two lectures given in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.103 DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Sound quality is poor; there is a buzzing sound throughout lecture (Item 98.104a)
  - "Emilio Ambasz Lecture: Poetics of the Pragmatic", March 14, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, 1989 PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Stuart Wrede, Director, Department of Architecture and Design, The Museum of Modern Art; Emilio Ambasz, architect SPONSOR: Gerald D. Hines Interests Architecture Program EXHIBITION:Emilio Ambasz/Steven Holl[MoMA Exh. #1511, February 9-April 4, 1989] DATA: Two 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (tape I: both sides; tape II: side I only) SUMMARY: Second of two lectures given in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.103 DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Sound quality is poor; there is a buzzing throughout lecture (Item 98.104b)
  - "Reflecting on Warhol", March 16, 1989; PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Emily Kies, Associate Educator for Public Programs, Department of Education, The Museum of Modern Art; Moderator: Walter Hopps, Director, Menil Collection, Houston; Amy Taubin, Film/TV Critic The Village Voice; Richard Sennett, Professor of Sociology and University Professor of the Humanities, NYU; Kenneth Silver, Associate Professor of Fine Art, NYU; Trevor Fairbrother, Associate Curator of Contemporary Art, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston EXHIBITION:Andy Warhol: A Retrospective[MoMA Exh. #1510, February 6-May 2, 1989] DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette (both sides) SUMMARY: Symposium held in conjunction with exhibition DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.105)
  - "Gallery Talk", March 28, 1989; PLACE: Gallery 16, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Kirk Varnedoe, Director, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 60-minute Standard Audio Cassette (both sides) SUMMARY: Side I: Picasso:Night Fishing; Girl Before the Mirror; The Herd; Seated Bather. Side II: de Chirico:Gare Montparnasse; Song of Love; Duchamp:R. Mott Urinal; Bicycle Wheel DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.106)
  - "Howardina Pindell- Artists Gallery Talks", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Howardina Pindell SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Cynthia Spurdle, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Howardina Pindell, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Romare Bearden RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.107)
  - "Izhar Patkin- Artists Gallery Talks", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Izhar Patkin SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Alexandra Anderson, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Izhar Patkin, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Kasmir Malevich RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.108)
  - "Ashley Bickerton- Artists Gallery Talks", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Ashley Bickerton SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Michael Schwartz, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Ashley Bickerton, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Donald Judd RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.109, 98.109D)
  - "Michael Young - Artists Gallery Talks", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Michael Young SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Gerrit Lansing, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Michael Young, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Mark Rothko RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.110)
  - "Robert Cumming- Artists Gallery Talks", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Robert Cumming SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Bobbie Duke, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Robert Cumming, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about his own work in current exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.111)
  - "Eric Fischl- Artists Gallery Talks ", May 4, 1989; PERSONALITY: Eric Fischl SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Chris O'Neal, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Eric Fischl, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Max Beckmann RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Side II contains an interview (Item 98.112)
  - "Contemporary Art in Context II: A Generation Apart: The Galleries", May 4, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Linda Shearer, Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Paula Cooper, dealer; Josh Baer, dealer SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: First Panel Discussion in a series of three held in conjunction with Contemporary Art in Context II RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.113)
  - "Contemporary Art in Context II: A Generation Apart: The Artists", May 5, 1989; NOTE: This sound recording was preserved in Fall 2004. In addition to the original, a 10.5 inch analog reel-to-reel archival master, a CD-R use copy and a CD-R back-up copy now exist.; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Kirk Varnedoe, Director, Department of Painting and Sculpture; John Baldessari, artist; Tim Rollins, collaborative artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Second panel discussion in series of three; held in conjunction with Contemporary Art in Context II RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.114)
  - "Contemporary Art in Context: A Generation Apart: The Differences", May 6, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Moderators: Amelia Mesa-Baines, Project Manager, Department of Integration, San Francisco Unified School District; Riva Castleman, Deputy Director for Curatorial Affairs, The Museum of Modern Art; Panelists Include: Fay Chiang, Director, Asian-American Outreach through the Arts, Henry Street Settlement; Daryl Chin, artist, critic, and writer; Kinshasha H. Conwill, Executive Director, The Studio Museum in Harlem; David Driskell, Professor of Art, University of Maryland; Allan Frumkin, Director, Frumkin/Adams Gallery; G. Peter Jemison, Site Manager, Ganondagan State Historic Site, New York; Luis Jimenez, sculptor; Inverna Lockpez, Director, INTAR, Latin American Gallery; Isabel Nazario, Program Analyst, Museum Aid Program, New York State Council on the Arts; Lorna Simpson, painter; Patterson Sims, Associate Director and Chief Curator, Seattle Art Museum SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: Three 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (both sides) SUMMARY: Third in a series of three panel discussions held in conjunction with Contemporary Art in Context II RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Tape I, Side I: the introduction cuts out right in the beginning; it resumes with first speaker (Item 98.115a)
  - "Contemporary Art in Context: A Generation Apart: The Differences", May 6, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Moderators: Amelia Mesa-Baines, Project Manager, Department of Integration, San Francisco Unified School District; Riva Castleman, Deputy Director for Curatorial Affairs, The Museum of Modern Art; Panelists Include: Fay Chiang, Director, Asian-American Outreach through the Arts, Henry Street Settlement; Daryl Chin, artist, critic, and writer; Kinshasha H. Conwill, Executive Director, The Studio Museum in Harlem; David Driskell, Professor of Art, University of Maryland; Allan Frumkin, Director, Frumkin/Adams Gallery; G. Peter Jemison, Site Manager, Ganondagan State Historic Site, New York; Luis Jimenez, sculptor; Inverna Lockpez, Director, INTAR, Latin American Gallery; Isabel Nazario, Program Analyst, Museum Aid Program, New York State Council on the Arts; Lorna Simpson, painter; Patterson Sims, Associate Director and Chief Curator, Seattle Art Museum SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: Three 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (both sides) SUMMARY: Third in a series of three panel discussions held in conjunction with Contemporary Art in Context II RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Tape I, Side I: the introduction cuts out right in the beginning; it resumes with first speaker (Item 98.115b)
  - "Contemporary Art in Context: A Generation Apart: The Differences", May 6, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Moderators: Amelia Mesa-Baines, Project Manager, Department of Integration, San Francisco Unified School District; Riva Castleman, Deputy Director for Curatorial Affairs, The Museum of Modern Art; Panelists Include: Fay Chiang, Director, Asian-American Outreach through the Arts, Henry Street Settlement; Daryl Chin, artist, critic, and writer; Kinshasha H. Conwill, Executive Director, The Studio Museum in Harlem; David Driskell, Professor of Art, University of Maryland; Allan Frumkin, Director, Frumkin/Adams Gallery; G. Peter Jemison, Site Manager, Ganondagan State Historic Site, New York; Luis Jimenez, sculptor; Inverna Lockpez, Director, INTAR, Latin American Gallery; Isabel Nazario, Program Analyst, Museum Aid Program, New York State Council on the Arts; Lorna Simpson, painter; Patterson Sims, Associate Director and Chief Curator, Seattle Art Museum SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: Three 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (both sides) SUMMARY: Third in a series of three panel discussions held in conjunction with Contemporary Art in Context II RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education; NOTE: Tape I, Side I: the introduction cuts out right in the beginning; it resumes with first speaker (Item 98.115c)
  - "Alice Aycock- Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: Alice Aycock SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Terence Eagleton, Member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Alice Aycock, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Constructivism RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.116)
  - "Bryan Hunt- Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: Bryan Hunt SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Jodie Eastman, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Bryan Hunt, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about work in permanent collection re: David Smith RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.117)
  - "Jenny Holzer- Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: Jenny Holzer SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Barbara Lane, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Jenny Holzer, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Merrit Oppenheim RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.118, 98.118D)
  - "David Diao- Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: David Diao SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Barbara Schwartz, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; David Diao, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.119)
  - "Emilio Cruz- Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: Emilio Cruz SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Kathleen Westin, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Emilio Cruz, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Czanne RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.120)
  - "Neil Winokur - Artists Gallery Talks", May 8, 1989; PERSONALITY: Neil Winokur SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context II PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Bobbie Duke, member, Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; Neil Winokur, artist SPONSOR: The National Endowment for the Arts; New York State Council on the Arts; Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Gallery talk given by artist about works in permanent collection re: Paul Klee RELATED MATERIAL: see index, Contemporary Art in Context DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.121)
  - "Minor White Lecture: Tracing the Artist", May 18, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Emily Kies, Associate Educator for Public Programs, Department of Education, The Museum of Modern Art; Peter C. Bunnell, McAlpin Professor of the History of Photography and Modern Art, Princeton University (Curator of Exhibition) EXHIBITION:Minor White: The Eye That Shapes[MoMA Exh. #1517, April 26-June 18, 1989] DATA: Two 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes (both sides) SUMMARY: Lecture given in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.123 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 10, 1998 (Item 98.122, 98.122D)
  - "Minor White Lecture: Sequences, Spaces, and Other Dimensions", May 25, 1989; PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Peter Bunnell, McAlpin Professor of the History of Photography and Modern Art, Princeton University (Curator of exhibition); Drid Williams, lecturer in the newly developed department of Dance and the Arts of Human Movement Studies, University of Sydney, Australia EXHIBITION:Minor White: The Eye That Shapes[MoMA Exh. #1517, April 26-June 18, 1989] DATA: One 60-minute Standard Audio Cassette (both sides) SUMMARY: Lecture given in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.122 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 10, 1998 (Item 98.123)
  - "Reading Cubism", November 2, 1989; PERSONALITY: Rosalind Krauss PLACE: The Roy and Niuta Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Lynn Zelevansky, Curatorial Assistant, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Rosalind Krauss, Distinguished Professor of Art History, Hunter College, CUNY, Coeditor October magazine EXHIBITION:Picasso and Braque: Pioneering Cubism[MoMA Exh. #1529, September 24, 1989-January 16, 1990] DATA: One 90-minute Standard Audio Cassette SUMMARY: Second of three lectures held in conjunction with exhibition RELATED MATERIAL: 98.125, 98.126a, 98.126b, 98.126c, 98.126d, 98.126e, 98.126f, 98.126g, 98.126h, 98.127a, 98.127b, 98.127c, 98.127d, 98.128a, 98.128b, 98.128c, 98.128d, 98.128e, 98.128f, 98.128g, 98.128h, 98.129a, 98.129b, 98.129c, 98.129d, 98.129e, 98.129f, 98.129g, 98.129h, 98.129i DONOR: Department of Education (Item 98.124)